JASPER JOSHUA GEOLAGON -

BS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

PROFILE

Hello I am Jasper Joshua Geolagon. For 9 years, I was a student leader, and for 4 years, I was a member of the school publication. My areas of expertise include article editing, broadcasting, and taking good pictures for memories. My experiences have shaped me as who I am today, broadened my horizons, and helped me develop my leadership and communication skills.



CONTACT

- **9** 0938-078-1186
- geolagonjasperjoshua@gmail.com
- Purok 1 Bitaugan, Antequera, Bohol

SKILLS

Writing

Broadcasting

Proofreading

Time Management

SOFTWARE

Canva

MS Office

HTML

CSS

LANGUAGE

English Language

Filipino Language

Cebuano Language

WORK EXPERIENCE

ibex

(October 2021 - February 2022)

Customer Service Representative

Worked at ibex a BPO company for 4 months as a CSR of Amazon handling Payment Methods of amazon users and Support in their mode of payment as well as retail queries providing refunds back to their original payment method and return of orders.

ZionLab IT Consultancy

(March 2023 - June 2023)

On the Job Training

Lead in the design, development, and implementation of the system, and website, Delegate tasks to the 5 members of the design team and provide counsel on all aspects of the project, and Supervise the assessment of all graphic materials in order to ensure quality and accuracy of the design.

EDUCATION

BOHOL ISLAND STATE UNIVERSITY - Balilihan Campus **BS Information Technology**

(2019 - 2023)

EXTRA CURRICULAR

Student Supreme Government Senator President

2021 - present

- Designed and Managed virtual programs at school.
- Organized weekly meetings.
- Suggesting activities up for the proposal.

Campus Journalism Associate Editor in Chief

2019 - 2020

 Reading and Editing articles to be published in the campus magazine.

School Performing in the Arts President

2014 - 2019

- Undergo conferences and seminars for the improvement of the club.
- Dance Training every Friday.

Student Supreme Government P.I.0

2016 - 2017

- Clean the areas after school events.
- Design the stage for an upcoming school program.
- Making memos up for the proposal.

Student Supreme Government Representative

2014 - 2015

- Attend meetings every Friday.
- Checking every room for the monthly category.
- Making certificates for the award every month.

REFERENCE

BENJAMIN N. OMAMALIN, PhD,CpE. College of Technology and Allied Sciences - Dean

Bohol Island State University - Balilihan Campus Magsija, Balilihan, Bohol

CHYLENE P. SARASPE, CpE. ZIONLAB IT CONSULTANCY, CEO

Guiwanon, Baclayon, Bohol

Hon. LEONARDA M. DABALOS Brgy. Captain

Bitaugan, Antequera, Bohol

I hereby certify that the above information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.

JASPER JOSHUA M. GEOLÁGON

Applicant